[
  {
    "section": "Seksi 1",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "What is the ISO 3297:2007 Certified?",
        "options": [
          "defined",
          "regression",
          "health",
          "healthy."
        ],
        "answer": "healthy."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the factors that affect calorie burning?",
        "options": [
          "tonnage",
          "burning",
          "nation",
          "average"
        ],
        "answer": "burning"
      },
      {
        "question": "In addition to machine learning, what other type of data is used to diagnose these problems?",
        "options": [
          "mining",
          "should",
          "alories",
          "study,"
        ],
        "answer": "mining"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 2",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "Under what license is this work licensed?",
        "options": [
          "Calories_individual",
          "under",
          "class",
          "Factor"
        ],
        "answer": "under"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the age of an individual mentioned in years?",
        "options": [
          "Celsius)",
          "Height",
          "weight,",
          "plots"
        ],
        "answer": "Height"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total amount of calories burned during a workout?",
        "options": [
          "Body_temp_individual",
          "Calories_individual",
          "learning",
          "store."
        ],
        "answer": "Calories_individual"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 3",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "What kind of license does this work have?",
        "options": [
          "Commons",
          "2393-8021,",
          "figure",
          "Engineering"
        ],
        "answer": "Commons"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is another name for Gender Distribution?",
        "options": [
          "Also,",
          "Attribution",
          "statistical",
          "Science,"
        ],
        "answer": "Also,"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the figure that shows the count of the gender in the dataset?",
        "options": [
          "dataset",
          "Journal",
          "Factor",
          "(figure"
        ],
        "answer": "(figure"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 4",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "IARJSET International Advanced Research Journal in Science, Engineering and what else?",
        "options": [
          "people",
          "Research",
          "Technology",
          "records"
        ],
        "answer": "Technology"
      },
      {
        "question": "In the same what direction?",
        "options": [
          "direction,",
          "correlation:",
          "\u00a9IARJSETThis",
          "3297:2007"
        ],
        "answer": "direction,"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a peek in the curve?",
        "options": [
          "unquestionably",
          "Research",
          "connected.",
          "means"
        ],
        "answer": "means"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 5",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "In what case is the XGBoost regressor used?",
        "options": [
          "process",
          "platform",
          "Creative",
          "case,"
        ],
        "answer": "case,"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the journal?",
        "options": [
          "correlation",
          "contrast",
          "committing.",
          "Kaggle"
        ],
        "answer": "committing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of calories are used in the X test?",
        "options": [
          "burned",
          "7.105",
          "results",
          "loaded"
        ],
        "answer": "burned"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 6",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "What is the effective method for predicting the calories burnt?",
        "options": [
          "Figure",
          "workout",
          "predicting",
          "Science,"
        ],
        "answer": "predicting"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term for a result of an event?",
        "options": [
          "2394-1588",
          "searching",
          "efficient",
          "RESULT"
        ],
        "answer": "RESULT"
      },
      {
        "question": "When was the data analyzed to make predictions about the number of calories burned?",
        "options": [
          "analyzed",
          "calories",
          "during",
          "Evaluation"
        ],
        "answer": "during"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Seksi 7",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "question": "What type of learning can ML be used for?",
        "options": [
          "calories",
          "(machine",
          "values",
          "accurate"
        ],
        "answer": "(machine"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the website?",
        "options": [
          "Information",
          "flexibility",
          "https://www.jetpac.com/",
          "[Online]"
        ],
        "answer": "[Online]"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the conclusion that the XGB Regressor produces more accurate findings?",
        "options": [
          "rates",
          "CONCLUSION",
          "other",
          "improved"
        ],
        "answer": "CONCLUSION"
      }
    ]
  }
]